sportswallah.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy - Sportswallah

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Sportswallah collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [www.sportswallah.com](https://www.sportswallah.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Sportswallah.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that isit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

**How do we protect your information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers. We do not use Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since all the browsers are a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

However, you will still be able to place orders .

Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third-party links**

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

**Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

We have implemented the following:

  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out:**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

  * On our Privacy Policy Page

Can change your personal information:

  * By logging in to your account

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails :

– Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

Email ID: [contactus@sportswallah.com](mailto:contactus@sportswallah.com)

Digiosmosis LLP  
3rd Floor, Gitaneel Arcade,  
Hill Road, Bandra West  
Mumbai 400050  
Maharadshtra, India
